kelbyone.com 2016-10-18

# Privacy Policy – KelbyOne

##### Privacy Policy

The last update to our Privacy Policy was posted on January 3, 2014. This governs the privacy policy of our websites and properties owned by KelbyOne, LLC

##### Our Privacy Pledge

This Privacy Policy applies to and is provided on behalf of the KelbyOne, LLC family of companies (collectively referred to as “We,” “Us,” or “Our”) and describes Our information gathering practices and policies in connection with this Site. We value your (“User,” “You,” or “Your”) privacy and recognize the sensitivity of Your personal information. We are committed to protecting Your personal information and using it only as appropriate to provide You with the best possible service, products, and opportunities. Use of this Site constitutes consent to Pages Our collection and use of personal data as outlined herein.

##### Definitions

“Non-Personal Information” (NPI) is information that is in no way personally identifiable and that is obtained automatically when you access our Website with a web browser.

“Personally Identifiable Information” (PII) is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained for us to provide you with a product or service. PII may include information such as your name, address, phone number, and other related information that you provide to us.

##### Our Commitment to Your Privacy

Our Privacy Policy tells you what PII we may collect from you, how we may share your PII, and how you can limit our sharing of your PII.

KelbyOne, LLC is committed to the security and privacy of all our customers. We take your privacy seriously, and we will work with you to ensure that you have an enjoyable online experience.

KelbyOne, LLC and our affiliates respect your privacy and recognize the need for appropriate protection and management of your PII you share with us.

As a part of our commitment, we have adopted the guidelines used by the Direct Marketing Association Privacy Promise to American consumers. Other than as necessary to provide you with goods and services, we agree to (1) provide our customers with notice of their ability to opt out of information exchanges with our affiliates; (2) honor our customers’ requests not to have their information transferred to our affiliates; and (3) honor our customers’ requests not to receive solicitations from our affiliates.

##### Links to Other Websites

Our Website may contain links to other websites. You understand that these websites are not under our control and are not subject to our Privacy Policy. These websites will likely have their own privacy policies. We have no responsibility for these websites and provide links to these websites solely for your convenience.

You acknowledge that your use and access of these websites is solely at your own risk. It is your responsibility to check the privacy policies of these websites to see how they treat your personal information.

##### Information We Collect

You can visit our Website without providing or revealing PII. However, we may receive and store certain types of NPI when you interact with our Website. We may analyze NPI for trends and statistics as to how people use our Website. Unless you wish to acquire goods or services through our Website, we typically will not require you to provide PII.

We receive and store PII that you provide to us when you place an order, register with us, send an email or call us, enter a contest, subscribe to a service, request to receive material, or participate in a promotion. In addition to your PII, we may also collect PII that you submit to us about other people, such as the name and address of someone you are referring to us. Ultimately, you have the choice in deciding whether or not to provide PII to us.

How Information is Used

We use PII that you provide for our internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration; analyzing statistics and demographics; and informing you of new products, services, and offers as provided by us and/or our affiliates.

Our affiliates may have products, services, or offers about which you may be interested in receiving information and they may use the PII we have for you to contact you. If you don’t want to receive information from our affiliates, you may opt-out at that time and let us know so you’re no longer contacted by our affiliates about their products, services, or offers.

We may also combine information you give us online or through printed forms; publicly available information; and information we receive from other parties. We use this combined information for your online experience and to let you know about new products, services, offers, and other promotion.

To give you the best possible service, we may use our affiliates to provide contracted services for our business, including, but not limited to processing credit cards, hosting our website, shipping products to you, or advertising. In many cases, we will need to provide some if not all the PII you provide to use so our affiliates can perform these services. Our affiliates are only authorized to use your PII as provided within this Privacy Policy.

There are times that we may have to disclose your PII to comply with state and federal laws; to assist law enforcement and governmental agencies in preventing or investigating fraud or other crimes, or in response to a court order. In such instances, we will only provide the PII requested and your PII will only be used for legal purposes as opposed to marketing.

##### Changing Your Information

You may change your PII at any time using our Website. If you need assistance with updating your PII or removing yourself from our mailing lists, just send us an email with your request.

##### Opting Out of Sharing Information

You can always opt out of future unaffiliated third-party disclosures of your information. Such opt-out will not affect disclosures otherwise permitted by law including but not limited to: (i) disclosures to affiliates, (ii) disclosures to third-party service providers who provide certain services for our business, such as credit card processing, computer system services, shipping, data management, or promotional services, (iii) disclosures to third parties as necessary to fulfill your requests, (iv) disclosures to governmental agencies or law enforcement departments or otherwise required to be made under applicable law, (v) previously completed disclosures to third parties, or (vi) disclosures to third parties in connection with subsequent contests or promotions you may choose to enter, or third-party offers you may choose to accept.

##### Protecting Your Child’s Privacy

We follow the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Even though our Website is not designed for use by anyone under the age of 18 (child), we realize that a child may attempt to access our Website. We do not knowingly collect PII from a child. If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child is using our Website, please contact us. We may ask for proof of identification before we remove any information to prevent malicious removal of account information. If we discover on our own that an unauthorized child is accessing our Website, we will delete the information as soon as we discover it, we will not use the information for any purpose, and we will not disclose the information to third parties. You acknowledge that we do not verify the age of our users nor do we have any liability to do so. If you are a child, please seek the permission of a parent or guardian before accessing our Website.

##### Our Email Policy

Our affiliates and we fully comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from us or affiliates. We will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission.

##### Our Security Policy

We have taken steps to build our Website using sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of your PII. When we collect your PII through our Website, we will encrypt your PII before it travels over the Internet using industry standards as establishing for conducting secure online transactions. We also use industry standard technologies such as secure routers and fire walls to make sure that your PII is safe. Unfortunately, we cannot fully guarantee secure data transmission over the Internet because of its nature. Once we receive your PII, we have industry standard security measures in place to protect against the loss or misuse of your PII, though again, we cannot fully guarantee against such loss or misuse. We strongly urge you to protect any password you may have for our Website and not share it with anyone. You should always log out of our Website when you are done using it, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.

##### Use of Credit Cards

You may have to provide a credit card to buy products and services from our Website. We use third-party billing services and HAVE NO CONTROL over these services. We use our commercially reasonable efforts to make sure that your credit card number is kept STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL by using only third-party billing services that use industry-standard encryption technology to protect your credit card number from unauthorized use. However, you understand and agree that we are in no way responsible for any misuse of your credit card number.

##### Cookies

Our Website may send a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of our site you have visited, so the next time you visit the site, we can better personalize the content that you see on our Website. Most browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to use certain functionality on our Website correctly or at all. We never place PII in Cookies.

##### Web Beacons

We may also use web beacons to collect NPI about your use of our Website and those of our affiliates, and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information we collect by Web Beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people that open our emails and why they opened our emails. Our Web Beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our Website or those of our affiliates. We do not link NPI from Web Beacons to PII without your permission.

##### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

As necessary to address changes in laws or our business practices, we may modify our Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, to address these changes. We will typically notify users by some message on our Website home page that our Privacy Policy has changed. We will also change the “Last Updated” date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically to make sure you still agree with it.

##### Questions about Our Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us using the Contact us information found on our Website.

By accessing or using the Site, You agree to be bound by all of the Terms of this Privacy Policy as posted at the time of Your access or use. We reserve the right to contact Users of the Site regarding changes to the Terms and Conditions generally, this Privacy Policy specifically, or any other policies or agreements relevant to the Site’s Users. If You have any questions about this Policy, You may telephone, email, or write to:

KelbyOne, LLCATTN: Privacy Policy Administrator  
118 Douglas Road East  
Oldsmar, FL – 34677  
Tel. 813.749.4000 x152
